(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Good news.
and bad news.
Which one first?
Broken.
I went to Fangfu Mountain.
but I couldn't find
that can change blood.
What's the good news?
I'm back safely.
This is good news.
What’s your next plan?
I want to rest
in Chong Ling Valley.
or keep looking
to change blood.
I found it.
Next, blood transfusion.
We found a clue.
There is a weapon
called Suncrossbow.
It was created by a master
by a master of Beixiang.
The crossbow
is fed on blood.
in the Blood Pool.
9981.
It was just out of the oven.
On the day of transmutation,
it drained
the blood of the real person.
Speaking of which,
Grandmaster,
I also saw the crossbow.
Back in the capital,
in the capital.
who fought with Ms. Xin
used this evil weapon.
I didn't expect
would be so useful.
I should have snatched it
in the capital.
Do you remember
the woman we met
at Ping’an Inn?
Two beauties.
are both pretty.
Which one are you talking about?
The one named Zuo Yingying.
She's from Qinghong Sect.
She went out with Mr. Ghost.
Mr. Ghost is dead.
Suncrossbow
is probably in her hands.
Let's go to Bei Xiang.
When are we leaving?
This time,
don't go with me.
No.
It's very dangerous to exchange blood.
And Qinghong Sect
is powerful.
I want to take back
from them.
It won't be that easy.
The power of Qinghong Sect
So what?
I have help
in Beijing Xiang.
Master has been in seclusion for many years.
I think
has reached a great level.
But even with her help,
I have to accompany you.
I made you.
After I transformed,
my cultivation has decreased.
You're also weak.
You can't maintain your human form for a long time.
You'd better find a place
and get some rest.
But I...
You and I have the same magic.
You can sense
you can feel it.
and help me.
right?
Don't worry.
Doctor Zhu Yu is not here today.
Senior Chen is in the hall.
Why isn't anyone here?
My illness
can only be treated by Doctor Joo Ok.
Right
Let others see it.
I feel uneasy.
What's the matter?
Doctors are human too.
He has his own business.
I made it in time.
It's the same for Senior Chen.
Is Physician Xu here?
Physician Xu will be in the court tomorrow.
If it's not urgent,
you can stay in the valley for a day.
Come back tomorrow.
I heard
the Herbal Lord Su Taiyi
made this Immortal Pill
It's not made.
The furnace exploded.
He's pissed off.
So angry.
I heard that
he hung himself.
Stop talking nonsense.
He died of old age.
How can an immortal
can die old?
I told you it's a stove.
In my opinion,
there is no such thing
immortality.
is a lie.
Now the road is broken.
No one can become a god.
Just live your life.
Is Chong Ling Valley
in Chong Ling Valley?
Let me see.
Why is it so hard?
Are you here to seek immortality?
Aren't you here to cure hemorrhoids?
You're the one with hemorrhoids.
It's not hemorrhoids.
It's a willow disease.
Screw you!
I just have a stomachache.
Gentlemen,
Which doctor are you looking for?
Do you have a brand?
No.
I have one here.
Come with me.
Go!
Go.
Let's go.
This...
It's in front.
Yeah, jump the queue.
We're in line.
Xin.
Let's talk.
Are you going back to the Immortal Sects?
A few days ago,
a big case happened in the capital.
A girl from the Immortal Sect killed four officials
and killed four officials in a row.
and led 12 cultivating sects
several warrants were issued.
and caused a lot of trouble.
In the end,
we can reverse this case.
and clear your name.
You told me everything.
and I gave you the answer.
Fine.
You got revenge for no reason.
You almost died after the surgery.
Have you thought about the reason?
What do you want to say?
Just be frank.
What I want to say is,
have you ever thought
you would be cursed?
Because there is a spell
can erase people's memories.
You met your savior.
without saying goodbye?
Do we know each other?
You're really...
If it weren't for me,
would you still be alive?
Last time,
It was me.
A sword
killed the centipede demon.
and saved you.
I forgot.
Senior Bai is waiting here
just to tell me this?
Yes.
Why?
I think you should know.
Where should I find the answer?
Maybe...
I'll be back soon. Thank you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
The magma flower of Mount Tianyuan has blossomed.
If you're on your way,
you can come back.
Miss.
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Are you feeling unwell?
Madam.
Where is this?
This is my home.
The doctor of Chongling Valley sent you here.
He asked me
to take care of you for a few days.
Chong Ling Valley?
We...
Yes.
I came with you.
There's a man
is making medicine for you in the yard.
Miss.
Slow down.
You just recovered.
Brother Yan.
Great.
You're not dead.
It's okay.
What happened?
Didn't you get beaten to death
in the formation?
Physician Su saved my life.
He just built a cenotaph for me
and treated me in the cellar.
A few days ago,
a few days ago.
Until recently,
until recently.
I wanted to find you,
But the doctor in Chong Ling Valley
knocked me out and took me out of the valley.
Luckily,
I'm glad you're here too.
But
why did Su Taiyi
save us?
Doctor Su is kind.
Besides him,
who else
to come back to life.
is just a pity.
Such a good person
died.
Dead?
When did that happen?
Just a few days ago.
Madam.
Did you hear it wrong?
No.
Many people went to worship him.
I saw it with my own eyes.
It can't be wrong.
What about
Immortal Pill?
Physician Su is dead.
who can make Immortal Pill?
Besides,
if he could really create Immortal Pill,
he wouldn't have died.
You've worked hard
to lead us to open the canal
and saved our village's herbal fields.
and our livelihood.
Now the royal tax has been cancelled.
Our future days
in the future.
Sir.
These
are
from us.
Please accept it.
Yes.
Yes, please accept it.
There's no need for a gift.
I appreciate
your kindness.
Please leave.
We
to thank you.
That's right.
Please accept it.
Take it.
No need to thank me.
This is all
owe you.
Goodbye.
Sir.
Don't go, sir. Don't go.
Let's go. Look.
We just want to thank you.
At least keep it.
Yes.
Be careful.
The sand is too soft.
Be gentle.
Don't drop it
Go that way.
Hold it.
Slow down.
Slowly.
Don't get hurt.
Be gentle.
Tang Yu.
Master Mei Shan.
Don't call me.
Pretend I'm dead, okay?
But that coffin
is a bit heavy.
The coffin is heavy.
What does it have to do with me?
You hired me
to keep you safe.
not a labourer.
Yes.
But when the coffin is stuck,
If we can't lift it out,
We can't go either.
Go?
Take me to the afterlife.
okay?
I...
I was the bounty guard.
I was dismissed
because of one case.
I thought
to be an armed escort
Being an armed escort
to make a living.
Who would have thought
I met a debt collector like you.
He asked me to escort you
to Beixiang.
You didn't pay me on the way.
I have to help you carry things.
to earn travel expenses.
I'm the No.2
in the martial arts world.
Not even a shelter
a shelter.
Poor me.
a sword that blows hair and cuts hair.
will suffer with me.
Blow the hair.
It's still working.
I'll get back to work.
Master, what's wrong?
This...
Use this.
I told you.
Don't follow me.
You're a demon.
I won't accept fairies
as my disciple.
Why, master?
We used to
at a picnic in the mountain
in the mountains in the city.
We fought the centipede demon together.
Look.
Bei Xiang is so big.
We've met each other.
What a coincidence.
Who's fighting centipede demon with you?
You are
with that demon.
I'm also a victim.
I was forced.
Didn't that nun say
I'm a good fairy.
I'm not on their side.
Master.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
They haven't paid me yet.
Look.
Do they look rich?
Master.
Bei Xiang is so big.
Let's find a place to stay.
You teach me swordsmanship.
I'll steal and support you.
If you don't learn well at such a young age,
If you dare to steal again,
I'll chop off your hand.
And...
Say it again.
I'm not your master.
Don't call me master anymore.
If you don't want to be my master today,
Maybe tomorrow.
From now on,
every day.
Maybe one day,
one day.
Let's go.
What are you doing, Young?
Are you a man?
Come and help.
I'm not going.
Ahn.
Help me.
I...
Okay.
She won't help you.
Let's go.
Let's go, master.
You stinky rabbit.
Hurry up.
How dare you push me?
Get up.
Chenzi is back.
Master.
Chenzi.
Senior.
Senior Sima.
Please remove your swords.
Grandmaster is waiting in the hall.
Everyone,
please come with me.
The path of nature is quiet.
Therefore, all beings are born.
The way of heaven and earth is soaked
So Yin and Yang win.
Yin and Yang will change smoothly.
Greetings, Grandmaster.
Master.
You're back.
I haven't done my job.
I've let you down.
I'm willing to be punished.
This matter is very tricky.
As a talented disciple of our sect,
you can’t finish it.
If it were someone else,
there might be a worse result.
Don't blame yourself.
Just go back and rest.
What?
Do you have something to say?
I have
I don’t understand.
During this trip to Chong Ling Valley,
I'll exchange the jade tablet
for Immortal Pill.
When the Immortal Pill was first created,
the Immortal Sects needed to
to Chong Ling Valley.
and distribute the jade tablets according to the contribution ratio.
But this time,
I found that...
the distribution of the jade token
is neither fair
and unfaithful.
Get up first.
Come to think of it,
there are 30 jade tokens in total.
only to all Immortal Sects.
and royal families.
can provide human resources
come from the people.
They gave up everything
but they couldn't get half of the jade token.
This is unfair.
Under the royal tax,
the people suffered a lot.
They even
live.
why do you want to be immortal?
It shows that
what the people have done
for Immortal Elixir
is forced.
This is injustice.
This is unfair.
Unfair.
Unrighteous.
and take the heavenly secret.
The elixir that troubled the people was born.
Is it right or wrong?
Su Taiyi failed in alchemy.
Is it good
or bad.
Everything can be explained.
What can I say?
I failed to cultivate the Immortal Pill.
and couldn't be born.
This has never happened.
Of course not.
Before we see the progress,
before seeing the progress.
How do you know
the result will be bad?
But now,
there's already a disadvantage.
What if the world is at a disadvantage?
what would you do?
will be ruined?
You're still young.
You don't know
is not right or wrong.
There are pros and cons.
You need to do your best to make profits.
A blade
It's bad to hurt the innocent.
It's good to get rid of the evildoers.
The knife itself is the same.
There is no right or wrong.
It depends on how to use it.
Who will use it?
Some die with food.
But food can't be forbidden.
Some are defeated by cars,
and restrict the ride of the world.
There's no definition between good and bad.
There's no law for right or wrong.
There's always a way
but not to do anything.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Based on my experience,
it should be here.
You can take this road.
Let me see.
This place...
Don't talk nonsense.
Listen to me.
Don't order around.
Look here.
You don't understand.
Just listen to me.
Biscuits again.
It's good to have food
We don't have enough food.
We have to buy more when we get back.
We're in the same situation.
You were hired too.
You're a practitioner.
You work hard every day.
Eat this.
You're still in a good mood.
What can I do?
Since we're here,
I know them.
You'll know when you get to know them.
They are nice.
A bunch of poor people.
More poor than me.
How good can he be?
Where's Ahn?
A ghost.
Ghost.
Master.
Master!
That coffin...
There's a ghost in that coffin.
What nonsense are you talking about?
There's someone in the coffin.
Nonsense.
Why not lie in the coffin?
The coffin is a living person.
Keep moving.
and smashing the coffin.
Master.
Kill him now!
There's no ghost in this world.
Could it be...
you want to trick Mr. Mei
to take you as my disciple.
It's true.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Okay.
I see it
Come on.
Have some pancakes.
It hurts.
Come in.
Master.
I called you here
to do something for you.
A few days ago,
a group of human beings
sneaked into our Collection Pavilion
and stole the books.
and hurt my disciple.
The possession of the demon
is very related.
I'm afraid he's up to something.
These people
to Bei Xiang.
Go now
to meet the disciples of Ilwol Cave
and capture them together.
I understand.
You stole something from the Collection Pavilion.
and hurt people.
No, Father.
I want to go too.
Stop causing trouble.
You're incompetent.
You've done more than enough.
I forgot
punish you just now?
In the capital,
I didn't run away.
It was an emergency.
I have something important to deal with.
Shiyi can be my witness.
Indeed.
I have something important to do.
Do you really think
I know nothing?
Chen.
You've been improving recently.
and are near the Golden Elixir Realm.
Don't let your guard down.
and delay your practice.
Yes.
Father.
Just stay at home.
and reflect on your mistakes.
Leng Ning.
Junior Jiang, wait for me!
Junior Jiang.
Bei Xiang, you go first.
Wait for me at the pass.
I'll find you in a few days.
Didn't Master ask you
to reflect on your mistakes?
Then I'll
sneak out.
It's hard to walk in the northern desert.
The terrain is dangerous.
How can I be at ease?
go there alone?
I can do it myself.
You'd better not make trouble.
What do you mean?
I was going to help.
Senior, you'd better save it.
Don't run away again.
They don't trust me.
They look down on me.
When I catch those demons,
I'll see what you'll say.
Master.
Do you think there's something wrong
with the coffin?
That coffin keeps making noises.
Maybe
something dirty inside.
I'm the second in the list of martial artists.
How dare you kill a demon?
I'm not afraid of your tricks.
I'll just die.
If you really scare me to death,
I'll fight you as a ghost.
Come on.
Don't pull me. What are you doing?
See for yourself.
What's wrong?
Can't you see?
There's no one in the coffin.
He can't always lie in there.
Do you know what you're talking about?
He's tired.
He went out for a walk.
Isn't that normal?
Master Yi Dao.
Who are you?
Don't fight back.
Don't shout.
You...
You know me?
Answer my questions
Answer me.
Okay.
This person is Lu Huai.
Do you know how to draw?
I can.
draw Lu Huai.
Okay.
Senior.
You knew it?
I went to the capital before I went to Chong Ling Valley.
I guessed something.
I was just not sure.
why he lied to me.
I have to ask Mr. Lu.
I bought this coffin
was bought by me in Central Plain.
I wanted to bring it back to Bei Xiang.
and bury it inside after I die.
and rest in peace.
But we have a rule in our hometown.
we can't leave this coffin empty.
Otherwise,
there will be something dirty.
If you move in,
you must find someone
who has strong yang energy
You need to keep lying in there to carry it.
How much did he pay you
How much did he pay you?
It's free.
He doesn't give you money?
We have enough wine.
That's why Warrior Lu is benevolent.
He calls you Warrior Lu.
Your surname is Lu?
Yes.
Lu QianQiao.
Feng Hong Knife
is my nickname.
I'll call you Brother Lu from now on.
Whatever.
Where's the elite brother?
Why isn't he with you?
He's busy.
Lu,
I still don't understand.
You help him.
without paying.
just to drink.
I was injured a while ago.
I haven't fully recovered.
I have something urgent to do in Bei Xiang.
I wanted to join Xiang with the caravan.
but I met them.
Actually, this coffin is quite comfortable.
If you're tired,
come in and lie down.
Thank you for your concern.
No need.
What about you?
Why did you come to Bei Xiang?
I...
It's a long story.
I've suffered more
than the sand on the ground.
These poor people.
They didn't pay me.
I have to spend my money for dinner.
I spent all my money.
you work as a worker to make money.
I, Mount Mei,
in the martial arts world.
a famous man.
I can't believe they're eating on their own.
Look at them.
They're so poor.
They even hired guards.
I wonder who wants to kidnap them.
Immortality tax.
[The number of people]
From the beginning of the birth.
A crying child.
From old age to dizzy
An old man who can't take care of himself
No exception.
In order to avoid tax evasion,
a better family
They don't get married and have children anymore.
In order not to
to avoid burden for the child,
and committed suicide by swallowing medicine.
Some abandoned their family
to become refugees.
All beings are equal.
But people are equal.
Three, six, nine.
Is this what you want?
you want?
Shin.
Do you still believe
the Crazy Taoist prophecy?
He said he was born on September 9th.
one of the best
there will be people who help the world.
I really believed
that person would be you.
Is this your plan?
to help people?
Do you really believe
what my master said?
Nothing is right or wrong.
It depends on how to use it.
who will use it.
I have a blade.
to protect myself.
but hurt people.
As long as the method is right,
it shouldn't be destroyed.
Even if this blade
was made from skeletons,
It was soaked
of the people?
Anything
will be sacrificed.
There are thousands of herbs in the mortal world.
Once the Shennong clan tries it,
it's inevitable to eat poisonous herbs by mistake.
This is also a sacrifice.
Is sacrifice
should be measured by numbers.
If there are more people,
Isn't that enough?
The Shennong family tried all kinds of herbs.
He sacrificed himself.
and the people.
who will sacrifice
Who sacrificed?
and who is beneficial.
Bai.
It seems
you still haven't figured it out.
Please...
Master, please enlighten me.
You have practised with me for years.
Although you are a genius,
but no pride.
Working hard is the most concentrated.
But because
it's easier for you
you'll easily
by some nonsense.
But what they said
really wrong?
Training Immortal Pill
did hurt the people.
Don’t we
sacrifice
No sacrifice?
Everything is mutual.
People feed the cultivating sects with supplies.
While when the war spirit came,
to kill the enemy and protect the people.
In terms of that,
our disciples
sacrifices are not inferior to anyone.
The government provided soldiers
to provide for soldiers to protect the country.
Don't you need money?
But we have paid
and got it.
As you said,
what will happen
what will happen?
If the people take Immortal Pill,
one can live at most.
But if
in our hands,
can protect the people
with one person.
Can't you tell
Can't you tell?
The elixir is in the hands of the strong.
it's good.
But what if
is not kind?
If it falls into the hands of the evil,
you can take it back.
Xiao Bai.
In this world,
in this world.
Kindness
evil,
and light,
there will be darkness.
We can't
we can't stop
will stop.
Although you still don't understand,
you don't have to hesitate.
Work hard
and improve myself.
to do
who can
to the weak.
Thank you for your teaching.
I understand.
I didn't expect
to be like this.
The real world is intertwined.
Inhale into the body.
You're really amazing.
Congratulations on your cultivation.
You’re promoted to the peak of Nascent Soul.
What’s the matter?
Grandmaster is waiting for you at Guiyuan Hall.
This time,
you are going to Beixiang.
to capture a group of devils.
Devils?
After the war between the gods and devils,
the gods disappeared.
the demons should have been killed long ago.
How can there be demons in the mortal world?
Demon comes from the heart.
Greed and hatred
will bring evil energy.
Humanity desires
can't be cut off.
These demons
stole
of Lingjing Mountain
and killed the disciples of Lingbi Mountain.
Now,
to Beixiang.
But they don’t have Immortal perception.
What's the use of
What's the use?
They
established an evil sect.
called Unstoppable Association.
They are extremely vengeful to the Immortal Sect.
They even
a large number of ignorant people.
spread evil religion
between the human race
and mislead the people.
They also adopted
with Immortal perception.
stole the cultivation of immortals
for children to cultivate.
as their help.
All these years,
they fought against the government
and killed the cultivators in secret.
and caused a lot of trouble.
They went to Beixiang
because of a magic spell.
The magic skill is hidden in Phoenix City.
in the Library of Phoenix City.
can disrupt people's mind.
and bewitch people.
If they succeed,
I'm afraid they'll make a big trouble.
By then, the world will be demonic.
We can’t kill them all.
We can't kill them all.
But the Sihe Library
was built by Qinghong Sect.
They are very powerful in Beixiang.
It doesn't matter.
I've sent a letter to Qinghong Sect
to Qinghong Sect.
Just do whatever you want.
I know.
I'll definitely stop the demonic cultivators.
I'll let the lamp
to go with you.
He is about to ascend to Nascent Soul.
and fought with the Demon-Enter many times.
It will definitely help you.
Remember,
these devils are best at disguise.
They usually like
to cover themselves
with a weak and kind appearance.
Then use words
with words.
You...
Don't be assimilated by them.
To prevent accidents,
catch him,
you can kill him.
Yes.
What do you want to know?
Who is he?
What's his name?
Why did you approach me?
Name.
This...
I really don't know.
I only know his surname is Lu.
So I know him
more than you.
But one thing
I can be sure that
he
to you.
That day, he took you
to the inn.
and take care of her day and night.
Ms. Xin.
He is really a good person.
At least,
he treats you well.
Senior.
Eat it while it's hot.
It's burnt.
Stop eating.
It's okay.
I like this kind of food.
Senior.
I went to a nearby village
and spent some money
to draw the public map of Bei Xiang.
There are three roads to Beixiang.
Only one official road.
The route for goods
is the road south.
But it's a bit far.
We have to cross two mountain walls.
The north road is short,
but it's just sandy roads.
It's hard to walk.
There's another west road.
It's longer than the north road.
But we can take half of the official road.
It's easier to walk.
Okay.
Let's go west